<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Avengers</string>
    <string name="hi">You’ll be able to watch Avengers: Infinity War a week earlier than expected.

Disney and Marvel Studios announced today that Avengers: Infinity War will be released on April 27 instead of the previously announced May 4. That means there will be even more breathing room for Infinity War at the box office before Solo: A Star Wars Story is released. Solo will be released on May 25.

Marvel Studios made the announcement via Twitter in a conversation with franchise star Robert Downey Jr. Downey Jr. will be returning to the Marvel Cinematic Universe to reprise his role as Iron Man in the new Avengers movie.</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>

    <string name="cp">In World War II patriotic solider Steve Rogers recipient of the "Super Soldier Serum" became the living symbol of freedom, Captain America. Left for dead while frozen in ice, the star-spangled hero with an indestructible shield awoke years later to continue his never-ending battle for liberty.</string>

    <string name="iron">Anthony "Tony" Stark was born to Howard Anthony Stark and Maria Collins Carbonell Stark, owners of the prominent US firm, Stark Industries. As a boy,
        Tony was fascinated with building and controlling machines. At the age of 15 Tony entered the undergraduate electrical engineering program at
        the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT), and graduated with two master’s degrees by age 19. Tony went to work for Stark Industries, but showed more interest
        in living a reckless playboy lifestyle than using his engineering skills. At the age of 21, Tony inherited Stark Enterprises when his parents were killed in a car
        accident secretly orchestrated by rival corporation Republic Oil (later ROXXON). Still lacking in business
        acumen, Tony promoted secretary Virginia "Pepper" Potts to be his executive assistant and left the majority of his workload on her so that he could avoid what he saw as a burden.</string>
    <string name="bw">Born circa 1928, Natalia "Natasha" Romanova was apparently orphaned as a child when she was trapped in a burning building during an early attack on Stalingrad by enemy forces. Ivan Petrovitch Bezukhov, a Soviet soldier, found Natasha in the inferno and rescued her. Although Ivan kept a close eye on Natasha as she grew, by the late 1930s she had attracted the attention of Soviet intelligence,
        which began her training. In 1941, she was almost brainwashed into serving the ninja clan the Hand, but was saved by Ivan, Logan (James Howlett, later Wolverine) and Captain America.</string>
    <string name="dt">Born in 1930, Stephen Strange was the eldest child of Eugene and Beverly Strange, then vacationing in Philadelphia. Two years later, Stephen sister Donna was born at the family Nebraska farm. At age eight, Strange was beset by demons controlled by apprentice sorcerer Karl Mordo, but was rescued by Mordo mentor, the Ancient One, a millennia-old sorcerer who protected the Earth dimension as its Sorcerer Supreme, a role Strange was destined to inherit.
        At age eleven, a year or two after his brother Victor birth, Strange aided an injured Donna, the experience inspiring him to pursue a medical career.</string>
    <string name="sl">Wrongly branded a traitor by his father Eson, Prince Jason of Spartoi fled the Empire, exploring deep space for many years. When war broke out between the Spartoi Empire and the Ariguan Confederacy, Eson summoned his wayward son home, but en route his ship converter blew. To avoid a complete meltdown, and with his ship apparently slipping backwards through time, Jason crash landed in Earth Colorado Mountains, his arrival witnessed by Meredith Quill, who dragged him from the burning vessel.</string>
    <string name="sp">Orphaned as a baby when his parents were killed overseas in a plane crash as U.S. government spies, only child Peter Parker was raised by his elderly Uncle Ben and Aunt May. Academically gifted, Peter displayed an uncanny affinity for science that was nothing short of genius. Socially, however, he was painfully shy and the target of much cruelty by his peers at Midtown High School. Attending a public science exhibit when Peter was 15-years old, he was bitten on the hand by a radioactive spider accidentally irradiated by a particle beam, empowering Peter with the arachnid proportional strength and agility, and the ability to cling to almost any surface</string>
    <string name="th">Thor is one of several powerful ancient beings who dwell in a magical realm called Asgard. Through history, these beings have been revered and worshiped as gods. Ages ago, Odin, lord of the Asgardian gods, desired a child who would one day exceed him in power. Odin wooed Gaea, the earth goddess, and from their union Thor was born in a small cave in Norway on Earth. Odin took him to be raised in Asgard by his wife, Frigga.</string>
    <string name="tn">On Saturns moon of Titan lived a colony of Eternals, and Thanos was born as one of the last sons of the original colonists, Mentor and Sui-San. However, he was born misshapen and monstrous in comparison to the other Eternals, particularly his handsome and carefree brother, Starfox, and Thanos grew into a melancholy, brooding individual, consumed with the concept of death. More than any of his people, Thanos sought out personal power and increased strength, endowing himself with cybernetic implants until he became more powerful than any of his brethren. At some point, he was exiled from his community, although the accounts differ as to its cause. Some say it was because he committed a crime by being the first to create a weapon. Thanos himself once claimed that he vivisected his own mother in an attempt to investigate how someone consumed with death such as himself could have come into being.</string>
    <string name="vs">Vision is an android who possesses a synthetic vibranium body created by Ultron and Helen Cho, along with the powerful gem known as the Mind Stone. Originally conceived as the perfect form for Ultron, the body was stolen by the Avengers, after which it was repurposed by Tony Stark and Bruce Banner, who uploaded the remnants of Stark personal A.I. J.A.R.V.I.S. into it. Upon his birth, Vision declared he was a mixture of Ultron and J.A.R.V.I.S., one that would fight to protect humanity at all costs. Vision then joined the Avengers in the Battle of Sokovia, using his powers to prevent Ultron from transferring his consciousness into the internet and allowing the Avengers to successfully put an end to him.</string>
    <string name="bp">TChalla is the current monarch of the African nation of Wakanda. As the Wakandan monarch, he is also the current holder of the Black Panther mantle. After his father was killed in a bombing attack orchestrated by Helmut Zemo, the new monarch set out to kill the Winter Soldier, whom was widely believed to be responsible for the attack. After being drawn into the Avengers Civil War and siding with Iron Man, T Challa learned the truth about Zemo deception and decided to help the Winter Soldier by granting him asylum in Wakanda.
After his coronation, TChalla began hunting down Ulysses Klaue, only to be confronted by his cousin Erik Killmonger, who sought the throne for himself. After a lengthy campaign, T Challa defeated Killmonger and decided to introduce Wakandan technology to the United Nations.</string>

</resources>
